forextester.com 2019-02-01

# All the ways we care about your privacy

### Last updated: October 22, 2018

Forex Tester, Inc. provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Data we receive from users of www.forextester.com (the “Site”)

This Privacy Policy applies only to information that you provide to us through the Site.

As used in this policy, the terms “using” and “processing” information include using cookies on a computer, subjecting the information to statistical or other analysis and using or handling information in any way, including, but not limited to collecting, storing, evaluating, modifying, deleting, using, combining, disclosing.

## Data Protection Principles

We promise to follow the following data protection principles:

  * Data Processing is lawful, fair, transparent. Our Processing activities have lawful grounds. We always consider your rights before Processing Personal Data. We will provide you information regarding Processing upon request.
  * Processing is limited to the purpose. Our Processing activities fit the purpose for which Personal Data was gathered.
  * Processing is done with minimal data. We only gather and Process the minimal amount of Personal Data required for any purpose.
  * Processing is limited with a time period. We will not store your personal data for longer than needed.
  * We will do our best to ensure the accuracy of data.
  * We will do our best to ensure the integrity and confidentiality of data.

### What Personally Identifiable Information do we collect?

We collect personally identifiable information from you when you place an order or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

### What do we use your information for?

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve our Site, services, features and content (collectively, the “Service”), to administer your use of the Service and to enable users to enjoy and easily navigate the Service.

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

  * To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
  * To send periodic emails  
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving updates, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

## How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order.

Forex Tester, Inc. takes reasonable steps to protect the Personal Data provided via the Site from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

We use safe protocols for communication and transferring data (such as HTTPS). We monitor our systems for possible vulnerabilities and attacks. Stored data is encrypted when possible.

## Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information).

All of the cookies used by Forex Tester are safe for your computer and they only store information that is used by the browser. These cookies cannot execute code and cannot be used to access content on your computer. They do not contain malware or viruses.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

Only we can access the cookies created by our website.

In addition, your browser or device may offer settings that allow you to choose whether browser cookies are set and to delete them. For more information about these controls, visit your browser or device's Help material.

Please note that if you choose to disable cookies, you will not be able to take advantage of all our features. We use Google Analytics to measure traffic on our website. Google has their own Privacy Policy which you can review [here](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245). If you’d like to opt out of tracking by Google Analytics, visit the [Google Analytics opt-out page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

You may voluntarily de-activate and/or eliminate cookies by following your Internet browser’s instructions below.

### How can a user block or eliminate these cookies?

You can allow, eliminate, or block cookies in your computer’s configuration settings according the internet browser are using. In certain cases, some web services will be blocked when certain cookies are not allowed to operate correctly or when they are blocked by the consumer.

These links explain how to deactivate or block cookies in common web browsers:

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### Do we gather any personal information about children?

The Service is not directed to individuals under 18. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Data without their consent, he or she should contact us. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Data, we will delete such information from our files.

### Your rights

You may exercise any of the rights described in this section by sending an email to support@forextester.com. Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before taking further action on your request.

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

We may need to update our Privacy Policy. The latest version of the Privacy Policy is always available on our website. We will communicate any material changes to the Privacy Policy.

### Contacting Us

If you cannot find the specific information that you are looking for about the privacy policy or the cookies usage, or if you have any other questions or concerns, please feel free to contact us anytime using the information below.
